AGORYE JESSICA

Phone: (+234)09063885307

Mailing Address

agoryejessical@gmail.com

Lagos, State 100001

As an experienced customer support associate and technical writer, I have a significant combination of skills that I believe would be beneficial in a web development role. In my previous role as a customer support associate, I honed my ability to provide exceptional customer service. Helping customers resolve their issues takes patience, empathy, and a willingness to go the extra mile, and all of these qualities I possess. I have a deep understanding of the products and services I support, and I am able to quickly and accurately provide customers with the information they need.

As a technical writer, I have experience creating clear, concise, and accurate technical accounts. I ascertain to conduct research and provide resources on the topics/ products I am writing about.

I am now interested in exploring opportunities in web development, where I believe my skills and experience would be valuable. I am proficient in HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, and REACT with an eagerness to learn new technologies and techniques. I am confident that my experience in customer support, technical writing, and technical skill set, would make me a strong candidate for web development roles. I am excited about the opportunity to apply my skills and experience in a new and challenging field.

EDUCATION

Gold Tech Computer School

Web Design

1

BSC

Houdegbe North American University

BSC Computer Science.

High School Diploma

St. Anthony Secondary School.

Primary School

A&T Nursery and Primary School.

WORK EXPERIENCE

VERPEX BLOG, FREELANCE WRITER. AUGUST 2022 – TILL DATE

- Research tech-related topics and trends.
- Create easily understandable content from complex concepts to present to both technical and non-technical individuals.

EDUKOYA, CUSTOMER SERVICE ASSOCIATE. FEBRUARY 2022 – AUGUST 2022

- Used knowledge base systems and work processes to help customers.
- Responded to questions and followed up on customer interactions.
- Placed outbound calls to existing members to provide additional consultation on products and services.
- Communicated with clients over phone, email, and chat platforms.
- Documented and classified member issues to implement proper service and solutions.

ACE EDU AND TRAVEL CONSULT, CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE YABA, LAGOS STATE. NOVEMBER 2019 – JANUARY 2022

- Managed an average of 30 calls daily, meeting targets which include: selling plans,
 managing customer accounts and resolving queries
- Negotiate and Manage Agreements with client resulting to a conversion of 10% of daily target.

PREMIERE CITY TUTORS, IKEJA, LAGOS STATE. CUSTOMER RELATIONSHIP MANAGER AND CONTENT CREATOR MARCH 2019-JULY 2019

- Managed customer relations on daily basis to maximize customer retention
- Assisted with conflict resolution
- Managed an average of 50 calls daily, introduced customers to current and new programs and services, resolved queries
- Delivered superior customer service to strengthen relationships and drive future business revenue
- Create and publish contents on company's social media pages.

STYLE RAVE (PART TIME), CONTENT CREATOR. STYLERAVE.COM JULY 2017 – MAY 2019

- Created, Edited, and Published Articles.
- Reviewed external writers' Articles before publishing.
- Researched and gathered data for content development.

• Developed strategies to increase traffic on the website.

PREPCLASS TUTORS, CUSTOMER RELATIONSHIP MANAGER. ALAGOMEJI, SABO, LAGOS STATE. JULY 2017- JULY 2018

- I Managed a daily base of accounts to contact at least 100 customers per day and consistently achieve revenue objectives.
- Trained team members and monitored activities to maintain the quality of services and enhance the effectiveness of offered solutions.
- Worked with CRM programs to track, review, and enhance business activities.
- Identified systemic issues and Managed customers' complaints.

SECRETARY / ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT, DOYIN AWOYALE & CO. SEPTEMBER 2016 – APRIL 2017.

- Provided variety of administrative support duties to the Managing Partner.
- Organized and set up meetings.
- Handled administrative tasks, such as filing, typing, and generating reports
- Ordered and oversaw office supplies such as paper, ink, etc.
- Took dictation, transcribed notes, and distributed meeting minutes.

PUBLICATIONS

Article

Jessica Agorye, "Best Online Payment Gateways" Verpex Blog, November 22, 2022.

https://verpex.com/blog/ecommerce-woocommerce-hosting/best-online-payment-gateways

COMMUNITY SERVICE

The Stellar Initiative

[Volunteer], [Lagos], 2022

LANGUAGES

English: Native Language

COMPUTER SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- CSS Framework(Bootstrap)
- JavaScript
- React.js

HOBBIES

- Reading
- Writing
- Hiking

REFERENCE

Upon Request